Kundwa Bruno Materne

Software Engineer

A well qualified Software engineer with progressive web skills familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages, Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 2+ years of related experience.

Work History

2021-09 -Current

Frontend Developer

Awesomity Lab, Kigali, Rwanda

- Reviewed project specifications and designed technology solutions that met or exceeded performance expectations.
- Worked with software development and testing team members to design and develop robust solutions to meet client requirements for functionality, scalability and performance.
- Work with variety of different languages, frameworks, platforms, and content management systems such as JavaScript, TypeScript, React, NextJs, Ant Design, AWS, Sockets.
- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Followed SDLC best practices within Agile environment to produce rapid iterations for clients.
- Contributed to projects within Scrum project management environments

2021-06 -2022-01

Fullstack Developer

Techenfold, Kigali, Rwanda

- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- Collaborated with project managers to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on pre-release software project development.
- Installation and deployment of developed

Contact

Address

Kigali, Rwanda

Phone

250-789-070593

E-mail

kundwabruno@gmail.com

Skills

Programming languages

- Javascript (ES5 & ES6+)
- Typescript
- Python

Libraries and Frameworks

- React Js
- React native
- Next Js
- Tailwind css
- Node Js
- Express

Tools and platforms

- Git
- Firebase
- Heroku
- Bitbucket
- Gitlab
- Github
- Netlify

- management software and website
- Designing of company website's frontend
- Integrate continuous feedback together with customers
- Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.

2021-01 - Engineering Apprentice

Andela, Kigali, Rwanda

- Attended training courses to build understanding of processes, techniques and industry.
- Shadowed senior team members to learn all related jobs and tasks.
- Worked within team using scrum on local bus transportation system web application
- Worked with local german company partnered with Andela as intern on E-learning platform. (Technologies used were: ReactJs, NextJs, Tailwind CSS, Node Js)
- Studied manufacturing processes to improve overall knowledge.

Education

2022-01

2021-08 -Current

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

Adventist University of Central Africa - Rwanda

 Elected to Technical supporter for school and computer labs softwares.